Finding Aid for the Finley, J. E. Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Finley, J. E. Papers
1920-1957
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0138
.42 linear_feet
Scope and Contents
The Finley Family lived in rural West Tennessee. The collection contains newspaper clippings that focus on farming and/or livestock problems, and the lyrics to old songs, which were published in the Commercial Appeal in the 1920s. It also includes a World War II Ration Certificates and Booklet.
- Booklets
  - Black Hawk Planters
  - Cotton Picking Book and Calculator
  - Future Farmers of America, 1934
  - War Ration Book Four – with stamps
- Certificate
  - War Ration Book One
- Correspondence
  - 1944-1945
- Membership Card
  - Cotton Marketing Card, 1950-1951
- Newspaper Clippings
  - 1920s
- Receipts/Statements
  - 1945-1957
Donor: Norma Riddick – January, 1993